<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>life on GDLP</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/tags/life/</link><description>Recent content in life on GDLP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gdlp.co.uk/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>my CV</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/cv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/cv/</guid><description>Gabrielle de la Puente, Liverpool
Writing, editing, curating, lecturing, chairing, consulting, teaching, mentoring, and just generally giving my opinion on all the culture that gets on my nerves (for better or worse)
✏️ Signed with Jo Unwin Agency
🎓 Studied BA Fine Art at Central Saint Martins
The White Pube est.2015 weekly reviews, essays &amp;amp; podcasts on art, games and other culture Successful Funding Application Library Selecting on the monthly Working Class Creatives Grant &amp;lsquo;Ideas For A New Art World&amp;rsquo; published with Rough Trade Books Critics Club school for criticism with Three Rivers, Bexley Advice Column for Elephant (ongoing) Advice Column for Dazed (ended) 2018 Global Initiative Speakers at Rhode Island School of Design Other writing Game writing on The Haven of Aves tabletop RPG for David Blandy&amp;rsquo;s Lost Eons series Report on The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist for Unlimited Writing for Vittles Season 3 The National Gallery commissioned a text of Eva Quantica Curation Founder and manager of OUTPUT gallery 2018-2021 Selection and critical support for Moon Games, part of Tour de Moon 2022 Assistant Producer at AIR for Tidal Twirlings, North Woolwich Founder and co-curator of Little Man Gallery 2015-2017 Other work University tutorials and lectures in art schools across the UK + internationally Mentoring artists behind the scenes I will add more stuff here when I remember what I&amp;rsquo;ve done or what else I wanna include</description></item><item><title>looking for a 1 day a week-ish job 🎯</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/tiny-job/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/tiny-job/</guid><description>Hey, I am looking for a one day a week job in arts/games/charity-work/idk what else. I used to run OUTPUT gallery alongside my work at The White Pube but I had to leave OUTPUT when I got Long Covid. I can&amp;rsquo;t go back to that job - it&amp;rsquo;s just too physical. I&amp;rsquo;m not 100% recovered but I&amp;rsquo;ve got enough life back in me to pick up a second job so I thought I&amp;rsquo;d write this blog post.</description></item></channel></rss>