<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GDLP</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/</link><description>Recent content on GDLP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gdlp.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>a beautiful staircase ✨</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/a-beautiful-staircase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/a-beautiful-staircase/</guid><description>deets:
Community Radio Tbilisi presents a monthly radio show A Beautiful Staircase in an Abandoned Building (ABSAB) by Ben Tupper, that explores the soundtracks of video games across various genres and console platforms. Each month, ABSAB features cuts of video game soundtracks curated around various cultural themes and selected by a guest artist with an affiliation for or working within video game culture. Video game soundtracks can be particularly unique in how they generate associations between memory, space and affect.</description></item><item><title>long covid treatment in Liverpool [UPDATED] 💀</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-liverpool/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-liverpool/</guid><description>I thought it would be good to keep track of how I have (and haven’t) received support for Long Covid in Liverpool. By good I mean useful for other people in the same position. By good I also maybe mean an interesting document for people with other post viral illnesses who are looking at the reaction to Long Covid and feeling some type of way. So, this is my shitty timeline.</description></item><item><title>ideas for a new art world 🌏</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/pamphlet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/pamphlet/</guid><description>this summer, Zarina and I released our first print publication as The White Pube in the form of a pamphlet for Rough Trade Books. It is #10 on their best seller list for 2021 which is cool!
You can purchase the pamphlet here: https://www.roughtrade.com/gb/the-white-pube/ideas-for-a-new-art-world/pamphlet-plus
&amp;lsquo;We are The White Pube and this pamphlet collects our ideas for a new art world. The art world is a bit broken. So many problems, such little time.</description></item><item><title>The Haven of Aves 🦢</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/the-haven-of-aves/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/the-haven-of-aves/</guid><description>Earlier this year, David Blandy invited me to write a supplement for his TTRPG series Lost Eons. This is the result:
Find The Haven of Aves here: https://davidblandy.itch.io/lost-eons-haven-of-aves
&amp;lsquo;A setting for LOST EONS based in a future Liverpool, an avian world of haves and have-nots. Featuring Art by Harriet Burns and a short story by Gabrielle de la Puente, enter a future world of water, misery and defiance.
Working with students at the Liverpool School of Art and Design at Liverpool John Moores University, Gabrielle de la Puente and David Blandy have created a future vision of Liverpool after climate collapse, that eerily echoes our own.</description></item><item><title>long covid and going nocturnal 🌙</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-nocturnal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-nocturnal/</guid><description>Sometimes I think, oh wait, I shouldn’t speak so openly about my health on the internet. My enemies will celebrate my bad luck; I might lose out on future jobs if people know I’m a little weakling nowadays! But I’ve found it really, really tough to follow along with any personal accounts of Long Covid and putting words onto the Internet might help others figure things out for themselves.
The words I want to put down today are about my sleeping pattern.</description></item><item><title>my favourite texts of 2021 ⭐️</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/best-of-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/best-of-2021/</guid><description>My first full year writing game reviews was a weird one - deeply concentrated on games, still understanding what they are and what they can do, all the while deep in my feelings becoming housebound from Long Covid. It was really helpful for me to write about being sick in order to process everything and make peace with it (if making peace is even possible). But I also resented writing about sickness, even when I felt the need to, because I hated how it would get stuck in my throat.</description></item><item><title>INFO</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/info/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/info/</guid><description>My name is Gabrielle de la Puente (b.94, Liverpool 📍)
I am a writer.
(✿◠‿◠) 🌸
I co-run The White Pube with Zarina Muhammad. On TWP, I publish criticism on video games and art. Reviews go out in text and we have a podcast for audio versions. We also run a Successful Funding Application Library and a Working Class Writers Grant. We think broadly about how we can make a better art world for everybody (one that is fair, accessible, and affordable).</description></item><item><title>Real Review 📚</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/real-review/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/real-review/</guid><description>I was invited to write about Long Covid for the Spring 2021 edition of Real Review. It was exciting because the Pope wrote something in the issue before me. I decided to look at all my symptoms, and reflect on how much my life had changed. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d sat down to write about LC and LC only, and it killed me to do so. At first, I actually regretted writing this because I haaaadn&amp;rsquo;t quite wanted to deal with how big of a change this had been for me.</description></item><item><title>The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist 👩🏻‍💻</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/art-report/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/art-report/</guid><description>Today, I am publishing the biggest thing I’ve ever written.
Download the PDF here: https://www.pdfhost.net/index.php?Action=DownloadFile&amp;amp;id=f42077e081d44f8b7a5bdbdc4d5fb4c4
It is a document called ‘The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist.’ Part report, it outlines how social media has become an important tool for work, networking and creativity. Part guide, it explains the differences between social media platforms, alongside tips, examples, and advice on safety and mental wellbeing online. Part conversation, it interviews different artists on their approach to social media (including Monique Jackson, v buckenham, the Kirkwood Brothers, Vince Laws, David Tovey and Babeworld).</description></item></channel></rss>