<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GDLP</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/</link><description>Recent content on GDLP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gdlp.co.uk/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>long covid and going nocturnal 🌙</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/blog/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/blog/</guid><description>Sometimes I think, oh wait, I shouldn’t speak so openly about my health on the internet. My enemies will celebrate my bad luck; I might lose out on future jobs if people know I’m a little weakling nowadays! But I’ve found it really, really tough to follow along with any personal accounts of Long Covid and putting words onto the Internet might help others figure things out for themselves.
The words I want to put down today are about my sleeping pattern.</description></item><item><title>Real Review</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/blog2/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/blog2/</guid><description>I was invited to write about Long Covid for the Spring 2021 edition of Real Review. It was exciting because the Pope wrote something in the issue before me. I decided to look at all my symptoms, and look at how much my life had changed. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d sat down to write about LC and LC only, and it killed me to do so. At first, I actually regretted writing this because I haaaadn&amp;rsquo;t quite wanted to deal with how big of a change this had been for me.</description></item><item><title>INFO</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/info/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/info/</guid><description>My name is Gabrielle de la Puente (b.94, Liverpool 📍)
I am a writer.
(✿◠‿◠) 🌸
I co-run The White Pube with Zarina Muhammad. On TWP, I publish criticism on video games and art. Reviews go out in text and we have a podcast for audio versions. We also run a Successful Funding Application Library and a Working Class Writers Grant. We think broadly about how we can make a better art world for everybody (one that is fair, accessible, and affordable).</description></item><item><title/><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/blog3/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/blog3/</guid><description/></item><item><title/><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/blog4/</link><pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/blog4/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>