<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Art on GDLP</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/art/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Art on GDLP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/art/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>coming to manchester to soon 💰</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/culture-is-bad-for-you/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 28 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/culture-is-bad-for-you/</guid>
      <description>on march 27th, I will be joining Orian Brook, Dave O&amp;rsquo;Brien and Mark Taylor at Blackwell&amp;rsquo;s in Manchester to discuss the updated version of their book Culture is Bad for You. You can book a ticket for the event here. This all came about because at the end of 2024, after being on a panel with Orian for Edinburgh&amp;rsquo;s Radical Book Fair, I posted a text about how much money I have earned as a writer since I began in 2015.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>on BBC radio London 🎙️</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/karim-bitar/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 30 Apr 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/karim-bitar/</guid>
      <description>we&amp;rsquo;re not actually allowed to do book promo yet because the october release is so far away but we managed to sneak in this one final interview before we have to keep our opinions to ourselves for a bit &amp;ndash; and it was a good one:&#xA;listen @ 1 hour 16 mins here -&amp;gt; https://www.bbc.co.uk/sounds/play/p0hnqnzr&#xA;Karim Bitar, of The Beat London, was invited to do a residency on Sounds of the City by Kim Davis for BBC Radio London, and he invited us along for an interview.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>tour of the john moores painting prize 🎬</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-tour/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 24 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-tour/</guid>
      <description>we filmed a video chatting through some paintings we selected for the John Moores Painting Prize show. I wish we could have spoken about more but we weren&amp;rsquo;t doing the edit. Show closes next monthhhhh</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>judging old art for fun 😈</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-19/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 16 Jan 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-19/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;ve been into top-down flicking-through-sketchbook videos on YouTube lately so I made this for fun:&#xA;you know when you do something and it&amp;rsquo;s like, yeah, no one asked me to do this, and no one will care, but I have to do it immediately? i love that feeling more than anything. I love to trust it!</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>made a video about judging the john moores 🎬</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-video/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Nov 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-video/</guid>
      <description>Art juror vlog. Niche content!&#xA;The show is on til the end of February. Hopefully you can see it IRL, if not, enjoy some of the paintings I feature in this video :))</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>every nando&#39;s is a gallery 🌶</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/nandos/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/nandos/</guid>
      <description>I just posted the special edition of The White Pube podcast that we made in partnership with Nando&amp;rsquo;s. You can listen or read the transcription here. It was a great and also genuinely surprising and uplifting week learning more about the company invests in Southern African art &amp;ndash; art, something no one in the world can truly expect a return on investment from. It&amp;rsquo;s support for support&amp;rsquo;s sake. It&amp;rsquo;s mad? and good?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>John Moores Painting Prize is open!</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-open/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 21 Sep 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-open/</guid>
      <description>Very happy to see the fruit(s) of my labour, and other people&amp;rsquo;s bigger, much more important labour &amp;ndash; the John Moores Painting Prize 2023 &amp;ndash; is now open for all to enjoy, after months of jury-ing and 1 afternoon of curation. Please visit! The show is excellent imo. It was a dream come true to be involved, and the resulting show is great thanks to the imaginations and persistence of the artists selected.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>spoke to BBC Radio 4 about taste</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/taste/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/taste/</guid>
      <description>Zarina and I had a chat with Zakia Sewell for her new BBC Radio 4 series &amp;lsquo;Taste.&amp;rsquo; We spoke about taste as an institutional force versus a personal one, our ethos with The White Pube, and why criticism is a sticky field in terms of power X_X&#xA;we&amp;rsquo;re in this episode: https://www.bbc.co.uk/sounds/play/m001ng7h&#xA;full series: https://www.bbc.co.uk/programmes/m001mt43/episodes/player&#xA;i like my occasional radio appearances. just seems so absurd :)</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A text for Adonis Archontides 📚</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sensing-is-believing/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sensing-is-believing/</guid>
      <description>A text I wrote in 2022 is finally out! The piece responded to Adonis Archontides&amp;rsquo;s artwork &amp;lsquo;Sensing is believing, believing is seeing&amp;rsquo; which was exhibited at the Nicosia Municipal Arts Centre in Cyrpus. The text is printed in booklets that open up into posters, so if you are lucky enough to pick one up in Cyprus, I hope you enjoy :)&#xA;The Past and the Present </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>in conversation with Abi Palmer ☔️</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/abi-palmer-invents-the-weather/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/abi-palmer-invents-the-weather/</guid>
      <description>You can watch the captioned chat here:&#xA;&amp;ldquo;Abi Palmer Invents the Weather is a series of four short films made by the artist Abi Palmer in collaboration with her two cats Cha-u-Kao and Lola Lola. These films premiere online on subsequent Thursday mornings in March and are followed each evening by a live talk show held between Palmer and special guests. For the third episode of The Weather, Abi Palmer will be joined by writer Gabrielle de la Puente to discuss rest, isolation, and animal companionship.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Art Basel Hong Kong 🗣</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-basel-talk/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-basel-talk/</guid>
      <description>on tue 7 march I was on a panel talk titled &amp;lsquo;Group Crit: On the Form and Function of Meme Making&amp;rsquo; alongside Hilde Lynn Helphenstein (aka @jerrygogosian) and Cem A. (aka @freezemagazine). The talk was chaired by Karim Sultan, and curated by Stephanie Bailey. I&amp;rsquo;m really grateful to Stephanie for bringing us together&#xA;a sneaky screenshot </description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a week in the life of a critic ✈️</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/critic/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/critic/</guid>
      <description>went to london for a week:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Kunstkritikk interview The White Pube 🫂</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/kunstkritikk/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Feb 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/kunstkritikk/</guid>
      <description>As The White Pube, we haven&amp;rsquo;t done a Big Proper Official interview in a while. To be honest, I didn&amp;rsquo;t have anything new to say. Everything already existed in tweets and reviews and whatnot, so we turned them down for a while. Now felt like a good time to reintroduce ourselves through a very measured interview with the Norweigan publication Kunstkritikk. You can read the piece here in English or Norweigan.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>liverpool day out 📸</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/liverpool-adventure/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 26 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/liverpool-adventure/</guid>
      <description>this was fun to make:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>come to ireland with me ✈️</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cobh-film/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 09 Jan 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cobh-film/</guid>
      <description>what i got up to in dec 2023:&#xA;unfortunately for the internet, and also my friends and family, my new year&amp;rsquo;s resolution is to film the things that happen in my life for the sake of posterity. also because I do love editing and I want an excuse to learn more things to do inside editing suites, they&amp;rsquo;re so fun</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>hello from a residency in Cobh 🇮🇪</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/sirius-arts-centre/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/sirius-arts-centre/</guid>
      <description>The White Pube is currently in residency in Sirius Arts Centre in Cobh, County Cork, Ireland. It&amp;rsquo;s our first official live-in residency in 7 years. We&amp;rsquo;re here for 16 whole days. It&amp;rsquo;s been very, very productive so far.&#xA;We&amp;rsquo;re writing a book at the moment, which is something I cannot speak about in earnest because of other people&amp;rsquo;s marketing timelines. But that is why we are here. Director Miguel Amado, who we&amp;rsquo;ve known for years now, got in touch to ask if there was any way Sirius might be able to support us at the moment &amp;ndash; not knowing about the book panic we were feeling.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>A-N Assembly on Access</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-n-assembly/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-n-assembly/</guid>
      <description>At the weekend, I was part of A-N&amp;rsquo;s Assembly Leicester weekender that focused on disability rights, DIY activism and working in the arts. You can read the full programme here which was led by Hannah Wallis and hosted by Two Queens.&#xA;I spoke on a panel titled &amp;lsquo;On Locality and Access in the Arts&amp;rsquo; alongside Ashok Mistry and chaired by Gino Atwood, discussing online localities, centralised social media, and the limits of digital activism.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Juror on John Moores Painting Prize 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-2023/</guid>
      <description>Very excited to be a juror on next year&amp;rsquo;s John Moores Painting Prize alongside Yu Hong, Claudette Johnson, Chila Kumari Singh Burman &amp;amp; Alexis Harding. And Zarina, obviously! I sent a quote for the press release but I will reiterate it here because &amp;hellip; who reads press releases &amp;hellip; not me&#xA;🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣&#xA;The White Pube’s Gabrielle de la Puente said: “When I had free periods in sixth form, my art teacher used to send me to the Walker Art Gallery.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>in conversation with lubaina himid &amp; co</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/found-cities/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/found-cities/</guid>
      <description>I recently chaired an event at Birmingham Museum &amp;amp; Art Gallery on the closing weekend of the Found Cities, Lost Objects: Women in the City exhibition. The panel comprised of Lubaina Himid, Sumaya Kassim, Dawinder Bansal and Selina Thompson. We spoke about existing in this country through a cost of living crisis, surviving in buildings and systems designed without women in mind. The talk was co-produced by BMAG and The WOW Foundation.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>ideas for a new art world 🌏</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pamphlet/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pamphlet/</guid>
      <description>this summer, Zarina and I released our first print publication as The White Pube in the form of a pamphlet for Rough Trade Books. It is #10 on their best seller list for 2021 which is cool!&#xA;You can purchase the pamphlet here: https://www.roughtrade.com/gb/the-white-pube/ideas-for-a-new-art-world/pamphlet-plus&#xA;&amp;lsquo;We are The White Pube and this pamphlet collects our ideas for a new art world. The art world is a bit broken. So many problems, such little time.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist 👩🏻‍💻</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-report/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/art-report/</guid>
      <description>Today, I am publishing the biggest thing I’ve ever written.&#xA;Download the PDF here: https://www.pdfhost.net/index.php?Action=DownloadFile&amp;amp;id=f42077e081d44f8b7a5bdbdc4d5fb4c4&#xA;It is a document called ‘The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist.’ Part report, it outlines how social media has become an important tool for work, networking and creativity. Part guide, it explains the differences between social media platforms, alongside tips, examples, and advice on safety and mental wellbeing online. Part conversation, it interviews different artists on their approach to social media (including Monique Jackson, v buckenham, the Kirkwood Brothers, Vince Laws, David Tovey and Babeworld).</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
