<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on GDLP</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on GDLP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2025 time 👹</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-time/</guid>
      <description>2020 was surreal, 2021 was the worst year of my life, 2022 was a mental hangover, 2023 was isolating but very creative, 2024 was social and vast and celebratory, and I hope 2025 is safe at the very least. But also rich. I hope 2025 is a moneybags year.&#xA;The Poor Artists book tour continues. I&amp;rsquo;m in Munich next week, then London Art Fair, and in Feb there are events in Bath and Liverpool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>everything I made in 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/</guid>
      <description>I did a blog post over on The White Pube about everything I made in 2023 across text and video, and reflected on how I managed to do anything at all given the fact my POTS is twice as bad as it was in 2022.&#xA;I also want to put it out to the Internet: if you are looking to give someone a 1 day a week job relating to writing, editing, social media, funding, community building or [insert the idea you had after reading the blog post aboout all the things I&amp;rsquo;m capable of] please get in touch on gabrielle@gdlp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my CV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cv/</guid>
      <description>Gabrielle de la Puente, writer in Liverpool.&#xA;For the first half of 2025, I am evaluating an NPO, and I have just started work as an Associate Lecturer at Central Saint Martins. My days are spent writing, editing, curating, lecturing, chairing, consulting, teaching, mentoring, and just generally giving my opinion on stuff.&#xA;✏️ Agent: Milly Reilly @ Colwill &amp;amp; Peddle&#xA;🏖️ Publicist: Lotte Hall @ Penguin&#xA;🎓 Studied BA Fine Art at Central Saint Martins</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
