<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Life on GDLP</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/life/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Life on GDLP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/life/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2025 time 👹</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-time/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 03 Jan 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2025-time/</guid>
      <description>2020 was surreal, 2021 was the worst year of my life, 2022 was a mental hangover, 2023 was isolating but very creative, 2024 was social and vast and celebratory, and I hope 2025 is safe at the very least. But also rich. I hope 2025 is a moneybags year.&#xA;The Poor Artists book tour continues. I&amp;rsquo;m in Munich next week, then London Art Fair, and in Feb there are events in Bath and Liverpool.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>everything I made in 2023</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 22 Dec 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/2023/</guid>
      <description>I did a blog post over on The White Pube about everything I made in 2023 across text and video, and reflected on how I managed to do anything at all given the fact my POTS is twice as bad as it was in 2022.&#xA;I also want to put it out to the Internet: if you are looking to give someone a 1 day a week job relating to writing, editing, social media, funding, community building or [insert the idea you had after reading the blog post aboout all the things I&amp;rsquo;m capable of] please get in touch on gabrielle@gdlp.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my CV</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/cv/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/cv/</guid>
      <description>Gabrielle de la Puente, Liverpool&#xA;Writing, editing, curating, lecturing, chairing, consulting, teaching, mentoring, and just generally giving my opinion on stuff&#xA;✏️ Agent: Milly Reilly @ Colwill &amp;amp; Peddle&#xA;🏖️ Publicist: Lotte Hall @ Penguin&#xA;🎓 Studied BA Fine Art at Central Saint Martins&#xA;The White Pube est.2015 Poor Artists, 2024, book published by Particular, Penguin in the UK &amp;amp; Prestel in US/Canada weekly reviews, essays &amp;amp; podcasts on art, games and other culture See Instagram, Twitter, recently resurrected Youtube Channel Podcast on Apple, Spotify + wherever you get your podcasts Successful Funding Application Library Selecting on the monthly Working Class Creatives Grant Juror for John Moores Painting Prize 2023 &amp;lsquo;Chaotic Nightclub Photos: The Review&amp;rsquo; published with Rough Trade Books 2023 &amp;lsquo;Ideas For A New Art World&amp;rsquo; published with Rough Trade Books 2021 Critics Club school for criticism with Three Rivers, Bexley Advice Columns Elephant and Dazed 2018 Global Initiative Speakers at Rhode Island School of Design Games Juror on 2023 BAFTA Game Awards - Multiplayer category Producer of Moon Games for Tour de Moon Game writing on The Haven of Aves for David Blandy&amp;rsquo;s Lost Eons series Teaching on Games Studies @ Leeds Beckett Other writing Column on Culture at Home for Elephant A text about the People of the Salt for Vittles Cooking From Life series Essay in Hardeep Pandhal&amp;rsquo;s book Inheritance Quest Report on The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist for Unlimited Writing for Vittles Season 3 National Gallery commissioned a text of Eva Quantica Curation Founder of OUTPUT gallery 2018-2021 Co-curation of John Moores Painting Prize 2023 Assistant Producer at AIR for Tidal Twirlings, North Woolwich Founder and co-curator of Little Man Gallery 2015-2017 Teaching Tutorials &amp;amp; lectures at art schools internationally Mentoring artists (on DYCP) </description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
