<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>writing on GDLP</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/tags/writing/</link><description>Recent content in writing on GDLP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gdlp.co.uk/tags/writing/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>publishing a pamphlet with Rough Trade Books 🍾</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/chaotic-nightclub-photos-the-review/</link><pubDate>Thu, 27 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/chaotic-nightclub-photos-the-review/</guid><description>in summer 2022, I published a 6k word review about a twitter account called Chaotic Nightclub Photos. I didn&amp;rsquo;t have much time to write it but I had fun. And then after I&amp;rsquo;d had my fun, Rough Trade Books got in touch asking if I would like to write a longer version as a part of their upcoming nightlife series. Yes pleaseee. More time to figure out what I wanted to say, more opportunity to put Gossip and Art History in there.</description></item><item><title>wrote another short story ooOoo</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/the-bingo-review/</link><pubDate>Wed, 05 Jul 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/the-bingo-review/</guid><description>okay, I&amp;rsquo;m on a roll, wrote another short story/review. This one is about the bingo. You can read or listen to it here:
https://thewhitepube.co.uk/games/the-bingo-review/
I don&amp;rsquo;t normally post about my TWP texts here on my personal site but I like the idea that someone coming to my site on a professional basis ends up reading the bingo review and thinking I&amp;rsquo;m mad
god speed</description></item><item><title>wrote a short story 👩🏻‍💻</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/wrote-a-short-story/</link><pubDate>Thu, 29 Jun 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/wrote-a-short-story/</guid><description>I haven&amp;rsquo;t posted any updates on this site for a few months because I got Covid in March and my health is in the bin again. I&amp;rsquo;m not even close to where I was energy-wise but I am doing more. Make of that what you will. One of those doing-more-things involved writing a bizarro short story over 3 afternoons. I am just&amp;hellip; a little bit sick of reality, I guess. Little bit sick of sincerity.</description></item></channel></rss>