<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GDLP</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/</link><description>Recent content on GDLP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The Haven of Aves 🦢</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/the-haven-of-aves/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/the-haven-of-aves/</guid><description>Earlier this year, David Blandy invited me to write a supplement for his TTRPG series Lost Eons. This is the result:
Find The Haven of Aves here: https://davidblandy.itch.io/lost-eons-haven-of-aves
&amp;lsquo;A setting for LOST EONS based in a future Liverpool, an avian world of haves and have-nots. Featuring Art by Harriet Burns and a short story by Gabrielle de la Puente, enter a future world of water, misery and defiance.
Working with students at the Liverpool School of Art and Design at Liverpool John Moores University, Gabrielle de la Puente and David Blandy have created a future vision of Liverpool after climate collapse, that eerily echoes our own.</description></item><item><title>The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist 👩🏻‍💻</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/art-report/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/art-report/</guid><description>Today, I am publishing the biggest thing I’ve ever written.
Download the PDF here: https://www.pdfhost.net/index.php?Action=DownloadFile&amp;amp;id=f42077e081d44f8b7a5bdbdc4d5fb4c4
It is a document called ‘The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist.’ Part report, it outlines how social media has become an important tool for work, networking and creativity. Part guide, it explains the differences between social media platforms, alongside tips, examples, and advice on safety and mental wellbeing online. Part conversation, it interviews different artists on their approach to social media (including Monique Jackson, v buckenham, the Kirkwood Brothers, Vince Laws, David Tovey and Babeworld).</description></item><item><title>long covid and going nocturnal 🌙</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-nocturnal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-nocturnal/</guid><description>Sometimes I think, oh wait, I shouldn’t speak so openly about my health on the internet. My enemies will celebrate my bad luck; I might lose out on future jobs if people know I’m a little weakling nowadays! But I’ve found it really, really tough to follow along with any personal accounts of Long Covid and putting words onto the Internet might help others figure things out for themselves.
The words I want to put down today are about my sleeping pattern.</description></item><item><title>my favourite texts of 2021 ⭐️</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/best-of-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/best-of-2021/</guid><description>My first full year writing game reviews was a weird one - deeply concentrated on games, still understanding what they are and what they can do, all the while deep in my feelings becoming housebound from Long Covid. It was really helpful for me to write about being sick in order to process everything and make peace with it (if making peace is even possible). But I also resented writing about sickness, even when I felt the need to, because I hated how it would get stuck in my throat.</description></item><item><title>Real Review 📚</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/real-review/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/real-review/</guid><description>I was invited to write about Long Covid for the Spring 2021 edition of Real Review. It was exciting because the Pope wrote something in the issue before me. I decided to look at all my symptoms, and reflect on how much my life had changed. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d sat down to write about LC and LC only, and it killed me to do so. At first, I actually regretted writing this because I haaaadn&amp;rsquo;t quite wanted to deal with how big of a change this had been for me.</description></item></channel></rss>