<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>GDLP</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/</link><description>Recent content on GDLP</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Juror on John Moores Painting Prize 2023</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-2023/</link><pubDate>Wed, 16 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/john-moores-painting-prize-2023/</guid><description>Very excited to be a juror on next year&amp;rsquo;s John Moores Painting Prize alongside Yu Hong, Claudette Johnson, Chila Kumari Singh Burman &amp;amp; Alexis Harding. And Zarina, obviously! I sent a quote for the press release but I will reiterate it here because &amp;hellip; who reads press releases &amp;hellip; not me
🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣🗣
The White Pube’s Gabrielle de la Puente said: “When I had free periods in sixth form, my art teacher used to send me to the Walker Art Gallery.</description></item><item><title>taught on Game Studies 🧩</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/game-studies/</link><pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/game-studies/</guid><description>In terms of teaching, I&amp;rsquo;ve only ever done lectures and tutorials for art students, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been winging it this entire time (winging it might be harsh, but lecturing on my work as the white pube feels innately like a fluke). So, it was nice to be excited down to Leeds Beckett to teach on Game Studies, and for it to not be a lecture but an actual 2.5 hour lesson.</description></item><item><title>mubi partnership 📽</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/mubi/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/mubi/</guid><description>I wanted to nip onto my personal site to share that The White Pube is doing a brief partnership with Mubi to promote the release of the African Desperate by Martine Syms. We are producing a review, social media posts, a podcast discussion in audio+video &amp;amp; we are also offering our readers 30 days of mubi for free. I&amp;rsquo;m a big fan of Mubi so I&amp;rsquo;m really happy about it and I&amp;rsquo;m sharing it here to celebrate :)</description></item><item><title>youtuber? ha ha ha</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/youtube/</link><pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/youtube/</guid><description>I spend so much time on youtube because i am on a friend&amp;rsquo;s premium plan, and I recently decided I should convert some content from The White Pube (which has been exclusively written + audio for years) into videos. Everyone loves videos. The algorithm loves videos. I love videos. So I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing things like this &amp;gt;
here&amp;rsquo;s a review in video form:
here&amp;rsquo;s a podcast in video form:</description></item><item><title>in conversation with lubaina himid &amp; co</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/found-cities/</link><pubDate>Tue, 13 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/found-cities/</guid><description>I recently chaired an event at Birmingham Museum &amp;amp; Art Gallery on the closing weekend of the Found Cities, Lost Objects: Women in the City exhibition. The panel comprised of Lubaina Himid, Sumaya Kassim, Dawinder Bansal and Selina Thompson. We spoke about existing in this country through a cost of living crisis, surviving in buildings and systems designed without women in mind. The talk was co-produced by BMAG and The WOW Foundation.</description></item><item><title>my CV</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/cv/</link><pubDate>Thu, 09 Jun 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/cv/</guid><description>Gabrielle de la Puente, Liverpool
Writing, editing, curating, lecturing, chairing, consulting, teaching, mentoring, and just generally giving my opinion on all the culture that gets on my nerves (for better or worse)
✏️ Signed with Jo Unwin Agency
🎨 Juror for the John Moores Painting Prize 2023
🎓 Studied BA Fine Art at Central Saint Martins
The White Pube est.2015 weekly reviews, essays &amp;amp; podcasts on art, games and other culture Successful Funding Application Library Selecting on the monthly Working Class Creatives Grant &amp;lsquo;Ideas For A New Art World&amp;rsquo; published with Rough Trade Books Instagram, Twitter, recently resurrected Youtube Channel Podcast on Apple, Spotify + wherever you get your podcasts Juror for John Moores Painting Prize 2023 Critics Club school for criticism with Three Rivers, Bexley Advice Column for Elephant (ended &amp;lsquo;22) Advice Column for Dazed (ended) 2018 Global Initiative Speakers at Rhode Island School of Design Other writing Game writing on The Haven of Aves tabletop RPG for David Blandy&amp;rsquo;s Lost Eons series Report on The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist for Unlimited Writing for Vittles Season 3 National Gallery commissioned a text of Eva Quantica Curation Founder and manager of OUTPUT gallery 2018-2021 Selection and critical support for Moon Games, Tour de Moon 2022 Assistant Producer at AIR for Tidal Twirlings, North Woolwich Founder and co-curator of Little Man Gallery 2015-2017 Teaching Tutorials &amp;amp; lectures at art schools internationally Teaching on Games Studies @ Leeds Beckett Mentoring artists (many on DYCP)</description></item><item><title>worked on a games project 🎮</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/moon-games/</link><pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/moon-games/</guid><description>99% of my work involves writing but every so often I get to work in a curatorial capacity. Tour de Moon got in touch to ask if we could find 4 young game developers under the age of 25. They wanted to commission people to make games that responded to typical game tropes, and they also had to use the zany aesthetic of the wider festival. Neon, marble effects, big shapes, abstract settings.</description></item><item><title>spoke to Teen Vogue about Long Covid</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/teen-vogue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/teen-vogue/</guid><description>i spoke to Teen Vogue about Long Covid. I re-read what I said and I thought &amp;lsquo;wow, that&amp;rsquo;s dramatic&amp;rsquo; and then stopped and realised how dramatic this whole thing really is.
&amp;lsquo;Since long-haul COVID left Gabrielle housebound, sometimes she finds herself wanting only to talk to other chronically ill people. “They’re the only people that get it,” the 27-year-old says. Her life — once so expansive, full of work, travel, and plans to learn to drive a car and visit new countries — has shrunk.</description></item><item><title>My Long Covid is actually POTS?</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-pots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-pots/</guid><description>A few weeks ago, I had an appointment with the Long Covid Clinic in Liverpool (that has recently changed hands, moving from Aintree hospital to a health centre in Speke). I described all the symptoms I’d been going through for the past year and the doctor said it sounds very much like I fall into the dysautonomic phenotype when it comes to Long Covid - - like the virus has messed up by autonomic nervous system and that’s why I &amp;hellip;</description></item><item><title>In conversation with Danielle Brathwaite-Shirley</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/arebyte-interview/</link><pubDate>Fri, 11 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/arebyte-interview/</guid><description>:)
Hope you enjoy the chat</description></item><item><title>a beautiful staircase ✨</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/a-beautiful-staircase/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/a-beautiful-staircase/</guid><description>deets:
Community Radio Tbilisi presents a monthly radio show A Beautiful Staircase in an Abandoned Building (ABSAB) by Ben Tupper, that explores the soundtracks of video games across various genres and console platforms. Each month, ABSAB features cuts of video game soundtracks curated around various cultural themes and selected by a guest artist with an affiliation for or working within video game culture. Video game soundtracks can be particularly unique in how they generate associations between memory, space and affect.</description></item><item><title>long covid treatment in Liverpool [UPDATED] 💀</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-liverpool/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-liverpool/</guid><description>I thought it would be good to keep track of how I have (and haven’t) received support for Long Covid in Liverpool. By good I mean useful for other people in the same position. By good I also maybe mean an interesting document for people with other post viral illnesses who are looking at the reaction to Long Covid and feeling some type of way. So, this is my shitty timeline.</description></item><item><title>ideas for a new art world 🌏</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/pamphlet/</link><pubDate>Fri, 10 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/pamphlet/</guid><description>this summer, Zarina and I released our first print publication as The White Pube in the form of a pamphlet for Rough Trade Books. It is #10 on their best seller list for 2021 which is cool!
You can purchase the pamphlet here: https://www.roughtrade.com/gb/the-white-pube/ideas-for-a-new-art-world/pamphlet-plus
&amp;lsquo;We are The White Pube and this pamphlet collects our ideas for a new art world. The art world is a bit broken. So many problems, such little time.</description></item><item><title>The Haven of Aves 🦢</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/the-haven-of-aves/</link><pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/the-haven-of-aves/</guid><description>Earlier this year, David Blandy invited me to write a supplement for his TTRPG series Lost Eons. This is the result:
Find The Haven of Aves here: https://davidblandy.itch.io/lost-eons-haven-of-aves
&amp;lsquo;A setting for LOST EONS based in a future Liverpool, an avian world of haves and have-nots. Featuring Art by Harriet Burns and a short story by Gabrielle de la Puente, enter a future world of water, misery and defiance.
Working with students at the Liverpool School of Art and Design at Liverpool John Moores University, Gabrielle de la Puente and David Blandy have created a future vision of Liverpool after climate collapse, that eerily echoes our own.</description></item><item><title>long covid and going nocturnal 🌙</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-nocturnal/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-nocturnal/</guid><description>Sometimes I think, oh wait, I shouldn’t speak so openly about my health on the internet. My enemies will celebrate my bad luck; I might lose out on future jobs if people know I’m a little weakling nowadays! But I’ve found it really, really tough to follow along with any personal accounts of Long Covid and putting words onto the Internet might help others figure things out for themselves.
The words I want to put down today are about my sleeping pattern.</description></item><item><title>my favourite texts of 2021 ⭐️</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/best-of-2021/</link><pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/best-of-2021/</guid><description>My first full year writing game reviews was a weird one - deeply concentrated on games, still understanding what they are and what they can do, all the while deep in my feelings becoming housebound from Long Covid. It was really helpful for me to write about being sick in order to process everything and make peace with it (if making peace is even possible). But I also resented writing about sickness, even when I felt the need to, because I hated how it would get stuck in my throat.</description></item><item><title>Real Review 📚</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/real-review/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/real-review/</guid><description>I was invited to write about Long Covid for the Spring 2021 edition of Real Review. It was exciting because the Pope wrote something in the issue before me. I decided to look at all my symptoms, and reflect on how much my life had changed. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d sat down to write about LC and LC only, and it killed me to do so. At first, I actually regretted writing this because I haaaadn&amp;rsquo;t quite wanted to deal with how big of a change this had been for me.</description></item><item><title>The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist 👩🏻‍💻</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/art-report/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/art-report/</guid><description>Today, I am publishing the biggest thing I’ve ever written.
Download the PDF here: https://www.pdfhost.net/index.php?Action=DownloadFile&amp;amp;id=f42077e081d44f8b7a5bdbdc4d5fb4c4
It is a document called ‘The Impact of Using Social Media as an Artist.’ Part report, it outlines how social media has become an important tool for work, networking and creativity. Part guide, it explains the differences between social media platforms, alongside tips, examples, and advice on safety and mental wellbeing online. Part conversation, it interviews different artists on their approach to social media (including Monique Jackson, v buckenham, the Kirkwood Brothers, Vince Laws, David Tovey and Babeworld).</description></item></channel></rss>