<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Games on GDLP</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/games/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Games on GDLP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/games/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>I was on a BAFTA jury 🎮</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bafta/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 30 Mar 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bafta/</guid>
      <description>I was on the 2023 jury for the BAFTA Game Awards for the Multiplayer category. I am very glad Elden Ring won. Chaotic choice in the eyes of some people, but I think it was doing the most to advance the multiplayer genre. &amp;lsquo;You need help and you can have help but only at great, finicky, risky cost&amp;rsquo; was so in keeping with the game&amp;rsquo;s narrative and challenge level. I was including the gamer-to-gamer peer-to-peer world that exists outside of a game, as well as the co-op that happens inside, and there&amp;rsquo;s no way I could have come to enjoy Elden Ring as much as I did without the player-built knowledge base around it.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>taught on Game Studies 🧩</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/game-studies/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Nov 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/game-studies/</guid>
      <description>In terms of teaching, I&amp;rsquo;ve only ever done lectures and tutorials for art students, and I&amp;rsquo;ve been winging it this entire time (winging it might be harsh, but lecturing on my work as the white pube feels innately like a fluke). So, it was nice to be excited down to Leeds Beckett to teach on Game Studies, and for it to not be a lecture but an actual 2.5 hour lesson.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>youtuber? ha ha ha</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Oct 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/youtube/</guid>
      <description>I spend so much time on youtube because i am on a friend&amp;rsquo;s premium plan, and I recently decided I should convert some content from The White Pube (which has been exclusively written + audio for years) into videos. Everyone loves videos. The algorithm loves videos. I love videos. So I&amp;rsquo;ve been doing things like this &amp;gt;&#xA;here&amp;rsquo;s a review in video form:&#xA;here&amp;rsquo;s a podcast in video form:</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>worked on a games project 🎮</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/moon-games/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 May 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/moon-games/</guid>
      <description>99% of my work involves writing but every so often I get to work in a curatorial capacity. Tour de Moon got in touch to ask if we could find 4 young game developers under the age of 25. They wanted to commission people to make games that responded to typical game tropes, and they also had to use the zany aesthetic of the wider festival. Neon, marble effects, big shapes, abstract settings.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>a beautiful staircase ✨</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-beautiful-staircase/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/a-beautiful-staircase/</guid>
      <description>deets:&#xA;Community Radio Tbilisi presents a monthly radio show A Beautiful Staircase in an Abandoned Building (ABSAB) by Ben Tupper, that explores the soundtracks of video games across various genres and console platforms. Each month, ABSAB features cuts of video game soundtracks curated around various cultural themes and selected by a guest artist with an affiliation for or working within video game culture. Video game soundtracks can be particularly unique in how they generate associations between memory, space and affect.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The Haven of Aves 🦢</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-haven-of-aves/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 07 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/the-haven-of-aves/</guid>
      <description>Earlier this year, David Blandy invited me to write a supplement for his TTRPG series Lost Eons. This is the result:&#xA;Find The Haven of Aves here: https://davidblandy.itch.io/lost-eons-haven-of-aves&#xA;&amp;lsquo;A setting for LOST EONS based in a future Liverpool, an avian world of haves and have-nots. Featuring Art by Harriet Burns and a short story by Gabrielle de la Puente, enter a future world of water, misery and defiance.&#xA;Working with students at the Liverpool School of Art and Design at Liverpool John Moores University, Gabrielle de la Puente and David Blandy have created a future vision of Liverpool after climate collapse, that eerily echoes our own.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>my favourite texts of 2021 ⭐️</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-of-2021/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 06 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/best-of-2021/</guid>
      <description>My first full year writing game reviews was a weird one - deeply concentrated on games, still understanding what they are and what they can do, all the while deep in my feelings becoming housebound from Long Covid. It was really helpful for me to write about being sick in order to process everything and make peace with it (if making peace is even possible). But I also resented writing about sickness, even when I felt the need to, because I hated how it would get stuck in my throat.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
