<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Long Covid on GDLP</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/long-covid/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Long Covid on GDLP</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-gb</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/long-covid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>The CHOP Protocol Diary 🩻</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/chop-protocol-diary-pots-long-covid/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 29 May 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/chop-protocol-diary-pots-long-covid/</guid>
      <description>I usually post work updates on this website but I wanted to share my experience of doing the CHOP Protocol somewhere, because whilst there are a few videos online, I struggled to find complete blogs that didn’t taper off after a few months. Also, my doctors don’t know what it is and maybe yours don’t either. I will return to this page each month to share an update for anyone interested.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>The labour government are doing eugenics 👉</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/pip-reform/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/pip-reform/</guid>
      <description>My current health crash has coincided with the big 5 year Covid-in-the-UK anniversary and with the Labour government&amp;rsquo;s new eugenic campaign. So I have been giving quotes to people, then reading them back thinking &amp;lsquo;I should have been meaner about all of this.&amp;rsquo;&#xA;I spoke to Creative Review about about the impact of Long Covid on the creative industry&#xA;I spoke to James Grieg for Dazed about how Labour&amp;rsquo;s benefit cuts will impact disabled artists</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>general sick note 🤡</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/soz/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/soz/</guid>
      <description>year 1 of long covid, I was practically housebound. year 2, I got the POTS diagnosis, medication for POTS, and I clawed my way outside. year 3, I got covid a second time, became twice as sick, and returned to life inside one room where I used what little energy I had remaining to write a book. Come year 4, I was dragged back out by a book tour because I was stupid enough to write a book.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>spoke to Teen Vogue about Long Covid</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/teen-vogue/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/teen-vogue/</guid>
      <description>i spoke to Teen Vogue about Long Covid. I re-read what I said and I thought &amp;lsquo;wow, that&amp;rsquo;s dramatic&amp;rsquo; and then stopped and realised how dramatic this whole thing really is.&#xA;&amp;lsquo;Since long-haul COVID left Gabrielle housebound, sometimes she finds herself wanting only to talk to other chronically ill people. “They’re the only people that get it,” the 27-year-old says. Her life — once so expansive, full of work, travel, and plans to learn to drive a car and visit new countries — has shrunk.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Long Covid is actually POTS?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/long-covid-pots/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/long-covid-pots/</guid>
      <description>A few weeks ago, I had an appointment with the Long Covid Clinic in Liverpool (that has recently changed hands, moving from Aintree hospital to a health centre in Speke). I described all the symptoms I’d been going through for the past year and the doctor said it sounds very much like I fall into the dysautonomic phenotype when it comes to Long Covid - - like the virus has messed up by autonomic nervous system and that’s why I &amp;hellip;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>long covid treatment in Liverpool [UPDATED] 💀</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/long-covid-liverpool/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/long-covid-liverpool/</guid>
      <description>I thought it would be good to keep track of how I have (and haven’t) received support for Long Covid in Liverpool. By good I mean useful for other people in the same position. By good I also maybe mean an interesting document for people with other post viral illnesses who are looking at the reaction to Long Covid and feeling some type of way. So, this is my shitty timeline.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Real Review 📚</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/real-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/real-review/</guid>
      <description>I was invited to write about Long Covid for the Spring 2021 edition of Real Review. It was exciting because the Pope wrote something in the issue before me. I decided to look at all my symptoms, and reflect on how much my life had changed. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d sat down to write about LC and LC only, and it killed me to do so. At first, I actually regretted writing this because I haaaadn&amp;rsquo;t quite wanted to deal with how big of a change this had been for me.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
