<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Long Covid on GDLP</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/tags/long-covid/</link><description>Recent content in Long Covid on GDLP</description><generator>Hugo</generator><language>en-gb</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://gdlp.co.uk/tags/long-covid/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>The CHOP Protocol Diary 🩻</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/chop-protocol-diary-pots-long-covid/</link><pubDate>Sun, 14 Dec 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/chop-protocol-diary-pots-long-covid/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;🤞🏻&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I usually post work updates on this website but I wanted to share my experience of doing the &lt;a href="https://www.dysautonomiainternational.org/pdf/CHOP_Modified_Dallas_POTS_Exercise_Program.pdf"&gt;CHOP Protocol&lt;/a&gt; somewhere, because whilst there are a few videos online, I struggled to find complete blogs that didn’t taper off after a few months. Also, my doctors don’t know what it is and maybe yours don’t either. &lt;em&gt;I will return to this page each month to share an update for anyone interested.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The labour government are doing eugenics 👉</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/pip-reform/</link><pubDate>Tue, 25 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/pip-reform/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;My current health crash has coincided with the big 5 year Covid-in-the-UK anniversary &lt;em&gt;and&lt;/em&gt; with the Labour government&amp;rsquo;s new eugenic campaign. So I have been giving quotes to people, then reading them back thinking &amp;lsquo;I should have been meaner about all of this.&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ol&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.creativereview.co.uk/long-covid-creatives-coping-pandemic/"&gt;I spoke to Creative Review about about the impact of Long Covid on the creative industry&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/li&gt;
&lt;li&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&lt;a href="https://www.dazeddigital.com/life-culture/article/66440/1/how-labours-benefits-cuts-will-impact-disabled-artists-welfare-universal-credit?utm_source=Link&amp;amp;utm_medium=Link&amp;amp;utm_campaign=RSSFeed&amp;amp;utm_term=how-labour-s-benefits-cuts-will-impact-disabled-artists"&gt;I spoke to James Grieg for Dazed about how Labour&amp;rsquo;s benefit cuts will impact disabled artists&lt;/a&gt;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>general sick note 🤡</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/soz/</link><pubDate>Sun, 09 Mar 2025 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/soz/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;year 1 of long covid, I was practically housebound. year 2, I got the POTS diagnosis, medication for POTS, and I clawed my way outside. year 3, I got covid a second time, became twice as sick, and returned to life inside one room where I used what little energy I had remaining to write a book. Come year 4, I was dragged back out by a book tour because I was stupid enough to write a book. I&amp;rsquo;ve just entered year 5 and I have crashed big time in a way that reminds me of those dark times in years 1 and 3. I have cancelled a bunch of stuff including some national and international work trips. I&amp;rsquo;ve kept a very minimal amount of stuff still on the cards over the next four weeks, and then idk. I think I have to do the work of being chronically ill &amp;ndash; I have to rest, have to get back to a good baseline, have to try new things to feel better, stop doing other things that make me feel worse. I am someone who always says yes to freelance work opportunities because I need to be earning money to live, but I am entering a time where I need to say no so I don&amp;rsquo;t get any sicker than I already am. I still hope the book pays off and we earn out and get royalties one day, but we wrote a book about art haha, it&amp;rsquo;s not a rom-com. So, if you are reading this because you have googled my name on a hunt for an email address to send me a work opp, still send it? I might have to turn it down if it compromises my health but it&amp;rsquo;s still nice to be thought of. I might be able to say yes if it&amp;rsquo;s accessible to the year 5 state I&amp;rsquo;m in, but we can talk about that.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>spoke to Teen Vogue about Long Covid</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/teen-vogue/</link><pubDate>Thu, 03 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/teen-vogue/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;i spoke to Teen Vogue about Long Covid. I re-read what I said and I thought &amp;lsquo;wow, that&amp;rsquo;s dramatic&amp;rsquo; and then stopped and realised how dramatic this whole thing really is.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;&amp;lsquo;Since long-haul COVID left Gabrielle housebound, sometimes she finds herself wanting only to talk to other chronically ill people. “They’re the only people that get it,” the 27-year-old says. Her life — once so expansive, full of work, travel, and plans to learn to drive a car and visit new countries — has shrunk. Now she only has the energy to deal with the present. “I can’t see what’s happening tomorrow or next week or a few years down the line. I can’t see if I’ll ever have kids because I can’t fully look after myself anymore. Everything feels futureless. And I think that futureless-ness is hard for people who aren’t sick to understand.”&amp;rsquo;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>My Long Covid is actually POTS?</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-pots/</link><pubDate>Mon, 21 Feb 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-pots/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;A few weeks ago, I had an appointment with the Long Covid Clinic in Liverpool (that has recently changed hands, moving from Aintree hospital to a health centre in Speke). I described all the symptoms I’d been going through for the past year and the doctor said it sounds very much like I fall into the dysautonomic phenotype when it comes to Long Covid - - like the virus has messed up by autonomic nervous system and that’s why I &amp;hellip;&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>long covid treatment in Liverpool [UPDATED] 💀</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-liverpool/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/long-covid-liverpool/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I thought it would be good to keep track of how I have (and haven’t) received support for Long Covid in Liverpool. By good I mean useful for other people in the same position. By good I also maybe mean an interesting document for people with other post viral illnesses who are looking at the reaction to Long Covid and feeling some type of way. So, this is my shitty timeline. And this is why I have lost faith in health professionals, or rather, the terribly organised structure that these health professionals work inside the NHS.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>Real Review 📚</title><link>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/real-review/</link><pubDate>Sat, 04 Dec 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://gdlp.co.uk/posts/real-review/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I was invited to write about Long Covid for the Spring 2021 edition of Real Review. It was exciting because the Pope wrote something in the issue before me. I decided to look at all my symptoms, and reflect on how much my life had changed. It was the first time I&amp;rsquo;d sat down to write about LC and LC only, and it killed me to do so. At first, I actually regretted writing this because I haaaadn&amp;rsquo;t quite wanted to deal with how big of a change this had been for me. But looking back, I&amp;rsquo;m glad it&amp;rsquo;s there. I&amp;rsquo;m glad I have these different bits of writing to track the year so far. Even if I have better words now, I have the first words there too, recorded, naive and sad. Anyway, here is the link and here&amp;rsquo;s a picture of the issue too. I was due to be in the summer issue but they wanted to bring my text forward (nice) except because it was a last minute change, my name accidentally got left off the list of authors on the back (bad) so you just gotta believe I&amp;rsquo;m in there lol.&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>